<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<meta xmlns="http://exist-db.org/xquery/repo">
    <description>A repository for EXPath Packages containing applications and libraries for eXist</description>
    <author>Wolfgang Meier</author>
    <website>https://github.com/eXist-db/public-repo</website>
    <status>alpha</status>
    <license>GNU-LGPL</license>
    <copyright>true</copyright>
    <type>application</type>
    <target>public-repo</target>
    <prepare>pre-install.xql</prepare>
    <finish>post-install.xql</finish>
    <permissions xmlns:repo="http://exist-db.org/xquery/repo" password="repo" user="repo" group="repo" mode="rw-rw-r--"/>
    <changelog>
        <change version="0.7.3">
            <ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <li>Fixed: Miscellaneous bugs.</li>
            </ul>
        </change>
        <change version="0.7.2">
            <ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <li>Fixed: Display of HTML pages when requesting packages compatible with older versions of eXist.</li>
                <li>Fixed: Increase timeout to 5 minutes when publishing apps to allow for re-scanning of larger repositories.</li>
            </ul>
        </change>
        <change version="0.7.1">
            <ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <li>Fixed: Issue preventing users from accessing older versions of packages when the newest release depends on a newer version of eXist.</li>
            </ul>
        </change>
        <change version="0.7.0">
            <ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <li>Feature: Allow lookup of packages by legacy abbreviations, e.g., abbrev=doc.</li>
                <li>Feature: Improve naming of XAR packages when downloading them via pkg.zip request, e.g., public-repo/pkg.zip?abbrev=doc&amp;zip=yes&amp;processor=2.2.0.</li>
                <li>Feature: Add a facility for describing found packages, e.g., public-repo/modules/find.xql?abbrev=doc&amp;info=yes.</li>
                <li>Fixed: Miscellaneous issues with changelog, icon width, focus of login form, loading landing pg without trailing slash.</li>
            </ul>
        </change>
        <change version="0.6.0">
            <ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <li>Allow processor version to end with a label, for compatibility with eXist 3.1.0+ semver scheme.</li>
                <li>Fixed links in atom feed by including min-version parameter.</li>
            </ul>
        </change>
        <change version="0.5.4">
            <ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <li>Fixed error affecting view of packages requiring different processor versions.</li>
            </ul>
        </change>
        <change version="0.5.3">
            <ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <li>Fixed issue with version number data type processing.</li>
            </ul>
        </change>
        <change version="0.5.2">
            <ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <li>New admin section to upload packages and publish them.</li>
            </ul>
        </change>
        <change  version="0.5.1">
            <ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <li>Fixed auto-upload.xql to consider only the xar type files.</li>
            </ul>
        </change>
        <change  version="0.5.0">
            <ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <li>Added support for automatic updating of apps.xml in case one adds, updates, or deletes a xar file from public folder.</li>
            </ul>
        </change>
        <change  version="0.4.2">
            <ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <li>Updated atom feed entries to link to each app's html page</li>
            </ul>
        </change>
        <change  version="0.4">
            <ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <li>Changed homepage display from grid to list, with separate detailed view for each
                    package</li>
                <li>Added display of change log to atom feed and detailed web view</li>
            </ul>
        </change>
    </changelog>
</meta>
